{
    "id": "dcd1cdaac0a14e5491d05c8622529ff7",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs With Put",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He can put ............................ gallons of Coke.",
            "description": "To put away is to consume food or drink in large quantities.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "in",
                "away"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "bfa3bddb939849bfbee45129da928d72"
        },
        {
            "question": "Criminals who pose a threat to the society should be put ............................",
            "description": "To put somebody away is to confine them in a prison.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "away",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "384bfce1a5f042089ee07b28509f8ad4"
        },
        {
            "question": "I donâ€™t like it when you put me ........................... in front of my colleagues.",
            "description": "To put somebody down is to criticize them.",
            "answers": [
                "down",
                "out",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9bfc5d0438f74f7f8f78ba398284d303"
        },
        {
            "question": "The police failed to put ............................. the riots.",
            "description": "To put down a riot is to end it by force.",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "out",
                "down"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "45857ca0613647c590ce4c0e64e5387d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Since the dog had hardly any chances of recovery, we had to put him .............................",
            "description": "To put down an animal is to kill it.",
            "answers": [
                "away",
                "off",
                "down"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b4846bd2c26c4fcebae77d020f918b0d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Her rude behavior put me ...........................",
            "description": "To put somebody off is to cause them to feel dislike.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "off",
                "away"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d4708971bedd441ca0ddf48952cd0b66"
        },
        {
            "question": "The exam has been put ...............................",
            "description": "To put off an exam is to postpone it.",
            "answers": [
                "away",
                "down",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "9ad4e725c18f493d89c07eb02ee2e50a"
        },
        {
            "question": "His insistence that I should lend him some money put me ............................",
            "description": "To put somebody out is to cause them inconvenience.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "down",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "631df5f8003c4ac89489d44374c9d80e"
        },
        {
            "question": "My cousin has agreed to put me ............................. when I visit Mumbai next week.",
            "description": "To put somebody up is to accommodate them.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "out",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "be05ca40b9de4fd4b3b888b505732a12"
        },
        {
            "question": "I cannot put .................................. his impertinence.",
            "description": "To put up with something is to tolerate it.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "out with",
                "up with"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "4747916642b84286acd3b28938010bcd"
        },
        {
            "question": "Dad is trying to put ........................... a fence around the garden.",
            "description": "To put up a fence is to erect it.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "out",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e7053bdfca394f1c952024a7ac75d789"
        },
        {
            "question": "If banks put ............................ their interest rates, it will hurt the interests of the economy.",
            "description": "To put something up is to increase its value.",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "up",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a3f1f83b277444709d4581070cc2a8ba"
        }
    ]
}